

Hunter Warren

hunterwarren.codes

hunter.warren@gmail.com

512.557.5032

About Me

OldLister

I'm a Front-End Developer who's transitioned to programming after 7+ years experience as an Advertising Art Director /Designer. What excites me about developing software is the potential to improve and enrich people's lives through the use of technology.

SKILLS:

Software Professional/Interpersonal **Programming** PHP / Laravel Photoshop, Illustrator, Visual design and mass MySQL, Git inDesign, After Effects, communication sensibilites Java (in progress) Premiere, Audition Presentation experience ES6 / React (in progress) • Excel, Google Sheets • Familiar with creative feedback HTML / CSS / JS • Powerpoint, Keynote process, and team collaboration

PROJECTS:

Using vanilla PHP, MySQL,
HTML and custom CSS, we
built a Craigslist clone allowing
people to buy and sell goods,
while allowing anyone to browse
what's for sale.

Using a Laravel framework, we built an analogue to the

Reddit.dev

we built an analogue to the famous 'front page of the internet' that stores users account info, and allows voting, ranking, and posting.

Globetrotter.pro

A mobile-responsive app for travel budgeting. Built with Laravel, we use PHP to call an API with cost data from 30,00 locations. User budgets are built with a jQuery and JavaScript 'wizard' and stored in a MySQL database, which is managed with Laravel.

WORK:

Previous Experience

2017-current

Front-End Developer at USAA

Worked within the Chief Design Office on a team of Front-End Developers of wide-ranging expertise to build pages for USAA's digital storefront. Most pages involve a significant degree of custom HTML, CSS & JS, as our team's storefront pages can't use frameworks or rely on external libraries. QA'd designs with their respective designers and project stakeholders, and with Accessibility Ops team. Uploaded all page code into Tridion CMS, and maintained CSS for other teams within Tridion. Contributed to a library of components used by our storefront FED's to faciliate rapid development of pages.

2014-2017

Art Director at DDB New York

Digital, Social, Video and 360 advertising campaign work for Clean & Clear, State Farm, Frigidaire, Electrolux, Lipton, Breyers, Exxon Mobil, and Royal Canin. Also responsible for digital content creation / content optimization.

2012-2014

Interactive Designer at DDB New York

Design work and UI/UX on mobile and desktop sites, and digital ads for: Frigidaire, Electrolux, State Farm, Reebok, USTA, RoC Skin Care, Aveeno, Lipton. Worked with developers to guide translation from design into digital product.

Education

SUMMER 2017

CODEUP

Completed 16-week software development immersive in San Antonio, consisting of 536+ hours of curriculum covering full-stack web development and associated technologies. Built various programming projects alone and in teams.

2007-2010

TEXAS STATE UNIVERSITY

San Marcos, TX. BFA Communication Design. Summa Cum Laude.